# Marek Sadura

#### Senior Full Stack Engineer (GMT+2)

linkedin.com/in/marek-sadura-epicode github.com/msadura sadura.mar@gmail.com +48 693737572 Software Engineer with over 12 years of professional experience in both front-end and back-end technologies. My aim is to develop software with the best quality, accessible UI, made user-first. Very enthusiastic about blockchain and web3 development.

#### Education -

MS in Computer Science

Lublin University of Technology

2006 - 2011

## Work Experience —

### **Principal Frontend Engineer**

#### Chainlink Labs - https://chainlinklabs.com/

2024 - Current

- Optimizing existing applications for Chainlink's ecosystem, focusing on speed, and smooth interaction with on-chain data.
- Improving the technology stack by integrating cutting-edge solutions and implementing industry best practices, driving innovation and ensuring best UX and DX
- Building standalone fullstack dApps for customers. Based on web3 stack, along with backend and database storage.

Main technologies: Typescript, React, NextJS, Ethersjs, Tailwind CSS, Node.js, HonoRPC, Prisma, PostgreSQL, Playwright, shadon

## Senior Full Stack Engineer

#### THORSwap Finance - https://app.thorswap.finance

2022 - 2024

- Implementing redesigned Decentralized Crypto Exchange interface using React, Redux, tailwindcss.
- Creating and delivering solution for Thorchain multisig wallet. Creating design system based on atomic components and storybook, considering mobile devices.
- Actively improving UI and UX, based on experience refactoring existing logic to achieve long-term sustainability.
- Integrating interface with THORChain api, providing announcements Node.js service. Implementing and designing lending interface Building Partners dashboard with wallet login, interactive charts and onchain data.
- Contributing to SwapKit open source library for handling cross-chain swaps by THORSwap

Main technologies: Typescript, React, NextJS, Ethersjs, Tailwind CSS, ChakraUI, Redux, Redux-toolkit, Node.js, tRPC, Prisma, PostgreSQL

#### Senior Javascript Developer

#### Sling by Toast - https://getsling.com

2017 - 2022

- Introducing React to the project, rewriting Angular JS web app to React. Designing React app architecture.
- Leading on mobile app development in React Native for iOS and android devices. Building CI pipeline for releases using fastlane.
- Working on improving product UI and UX, using best code practises and building base components based on design system.

Main technologies: Typescript, React, React Native, Redux, Rxjs, Styled Components, Storybook, Jest, Mocha

#### Senior Software Developer

#### Intive.com (previously BLStream Sp. z o.o.)

2014 - 2017

- Building the official Oscars website in Angular JS <a href="https://oscars.go.com/">https://oscars.go.com/</a>
- Implementing SEO friendly AngularJS app with pre-rendering content on the server.
- Working close to the customer, gathering requirements and implementing functionalities under the pressure of time.

Main technologies: Typescript, AngularJS, React, Mocha, Less, Redux, AWS

#### Software Developer

#### Select Sp. Z o.o.

2011 - 2014

- Customizing ZenCart based ecommerce platforms.
- Supporting and expanding functionalities of CRM systems based on SugarCRM, introducing AngularJS to the project.
- Implementing designs and RWD interfaces.

Main technologies: PHP, MySQL, Javascript, CSSs, AngularJS, nginx

# **Projects**

Founder stake.com.ai 2024

- Developing a staking dApp for CommuneAl (Bittensor fork), enabling the staking of wrapped EVM tokens natively on the Commune chain.
- Leveraging official bridge and building EVM smart contracts to facilitate seamless staking operations on the native chain.
- Authoring and open-sourcing a TypeScript library to interact with the Commune RPC (Polkadot substrate), enhancing the developer ecosystem and supporting broader community adoption.

Main technologies: React, Next.js, Nodejs, Solidity, Hardhat, wagmi, PolkadotJS